If you look at the insurance space, the
company seems to be making significant gains, especially in motor insurance. For
this reason, I believe that
ISI Lod could be a very good name in the non-life insurance space. Of course, if
you look at the parent,
IIC Bank also seems to be having a good share in it. The
company's return on capital employed is also 22.5%.
You have seen good action in the stock price as well. The
share of AI and DI is also quite
comfortable. They
also seem to be combining holdings of approximately more than 40%.
So, the expectations are that
you should invest here for the long term. The
insurance space is already very
good, and especially now, the way
technologies are developing,
it can be a big region for the insurance space.
From this and further distribution perspective,
IIC Lombard is
a good bet in the general insurance space. ₹2500000 in the next 12 months.
Shop for Tuts here